prepinsta.com 2018-11-30

# Privacy Policy » Prep Insta

## **Privacy policy**

We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of information that apply to our Service, as well as your choices regarding the collection and use of information. It is important that you read this Privacy Policy together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy notice supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them.

##  **  Applicability and third-party websites and services**

This Privacy Policy only applies to the information we collect when you use the Service or view the comments and does not apply to any website that uses the Service or other website linked to from the Service. We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, including Partner Sites, or the information or content contained thereon. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer applicable, it also does not apply to the Partner Site on which you are commenting. Your browsing activity and interaction with any other website, including those that you link to from the Service, is subject to that website’s privacy policy.

##  **The Data we Collect About You**

Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).

We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped as follows:

  *  **Identity Data  **includes first name, last name, username or similar identifier, and date of birth.
  *  **Contact Data  **includes an email address and telephone numbers, and mailing address.
  *  **Technical Data  **includes internet protocol (IP) address, unique Cookie ID, Device ID, your login data, browser type, and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access the Service.
  *  **Profile Data  **includes your username and password, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses, marital status, gender, title.
  *  **Usage Data  **includes information about how you use the Service.

  1. We also collect, use and share Aggregated Data such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Aggregated Data may be derived from your data but is not considered personal data in law as this data does not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific service feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this privacy notice.
  2. We do not collect any Special Categories of Personal Data about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offenses.
  3. Where we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with the Service). In this case, we may have to cancel the Service, but we will notify you if this is the case at the time.

##  **Cookies**

 ** ** A cookie is a small piece of data that is stored on your computer or mobile device. When you use the Service or visit a Partner Site using the Service, we send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Cookies help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. We use cookies to collect information about how you use the Service (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take), to track your usage of the Service, and to personalize the content we show you, including ads. We may use both persistent cookies, which remain on your hard drive after you close your browser and session cookies which terminate when you close your browser. Many browser settings can be set to decline cookies or alert you when a website is attempting to place a cookie. If you have questions about such functionalities, you should consult with your browser’s manufacturer. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

##  **Links to the Other Sites**

Our policy discloses the privacy practices for our web site only. Our site provides links to other websites also that are beyond our control. We shall in no way be responsible in a way for your use of such sites.

##  **Information Sharing**

We share the sensitive personal information to any third party without obtaining the prior consent of the user in the following limited circumstances:

 **(a)**  When it is requested or required by law or by any court or governmental agency or authority to disclose, for verification of identity, or for the prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, or for prosecution and punishment of offenses. These disclosures are made in good faith and belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary for enforcing these Terms; for complying with the applicable laws and regulations.

 **(b)**  We propose to share such information within its group companies and officers and employees of such group companies for processing personal information on its behalf. We also ensure that these recipients of such information agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

##  **Information Security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

All information gathered on our Website is securely stored within our controlled database. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone with Internet access.

However, the internet is an ever evolving medium. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.
